https://www.oneupweb.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to main content
Effective date: December 09, 2011 Oneupweb (“we,” “us” or “our”) respects your privacy. It’s so important, we’ve developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, and protect your information and how you can correct inaccuracies in the contact information you provide. Please take time to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have questions. We’ll be happy to answer them. By visiting and using Oneupweb.com (the “website”), you indicate your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and the collection, management and use of your personal information as described below. We encourage you to check this Privacy Policy periodically, as we may make changes to the Privacy Policy from time to time. We reserve the right to revise this policy at any time by updating this posting without advance notice to you. The revisions are effective immediately. Your continued use of the website constitutes your acceptance to any revisions of this Privacy Policy.
What Information is Collected
Voluntarily submitted information
When you submit a form requesting our research papers, studies, newsletters, other resources and/or requesting some information or correspondence, we sometimes ask you for your name, company name, email address, postal address, phone and/or other information. Voluntarily submitted information may be subject to additional terms and restrictions agreed upon at the time the information was submitted. Oneupweb collects and stores all voluntarily submitted information.
Information from our web server logs
When you visit most any internet website, you automatically disclose certain limited information about yourself, such as your internet protocol (IP) address, the time of your visit and the referring location (e.g., the website or page that offered a link to a Oneupweb page). Information that can potentially be collected when you visit our website includes, but is not limited to: IP address, referring location and operating system information and various browser details. Oneupweb collects and stores all information automatically generated as you navigate our website.
How and When Information is Used
Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single, specific person. Oneupweb does not knowingly make your personal information available to any third parties without your permission. When you provide personal information to us, we may use that information in one or more of the following ways:
For the purpose for which it was provided (e.g., to provide services to you, contact you regarding services, to respond to your problems and comments);For system administration and other internal purposes, such as to improve our website and content or for internal data analysis and research;To keep you updated on Oneupweb’s latest developments or to contact you for other informational, marketing or promotional purposes;When we believe in good faith that release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our terms and conditions or to protect the rights, property or safety of users of this website or the public.
While your personal information helps us keep in contact with you and stay in touch with our users, we respect your decision not to be contacted by us in the future. You may opt out at any time. If you wish to opt out of future communications, please let us know by emailing us at info@oneupweb.com (please include “Do Not Contact” in the subject line) or by writing to: Oneupweb Attn: Privacy Policy Administrator 1371 Gray Drive, Suite 100 Traverse City, MI 49684
How We Use Your Non-Personal Information
Non-personal data is data that does not permit direct association with any single, specific individual. Non-personal data includes, but is not limited to, language, location, occupation, zip code and area code. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose, including providing aggregate non-personal information to third parties. Some examples of use include, but are not limited to, analyzing our website traffic and understanding which parts of our website or services are of most interest. In the event that we combine non-personal information with personal information, the combined information is treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.
How We Use “Cookies” and Other Technologies
We may use “cookies” (small data files that assign you a unique identifier) and other technologies, such as pixel tags and web beacons, to help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our website people have visited and to measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. This information is non-personal information; however, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. You may use your browser’s preferences to disable cookies, but understand that by doing so, you may cause certain aspects of the website to operate incorrectly or otherwise limit the functionality of the website. Third parties that link on this site may use cookies or collect other information when you go to their site. We do not control the collection or use of your information by these companies. You should contact these companies directly if you have any questions about their collection or use of information about you.
How We Protect Your Information
We utilize appropriate security measures to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, misuse and alteration. We make reasonable efforts to protect the security of your personally-identifiable information and periodically review and enhance these methods as necessary. However, we make no guarantee that unauthorized, inadvertent disclosures will never occur. All submissions of information by you on our website are made at your own risk.
How Can I Correct Inaccuracies In My Information?
You may request to correct inaccuracies in your contact information. To submit corrections to your contact information please email us at info@oneupweb.com. Please include “Contact Information Correction” in the subject line of your email message. You may also submit your corrections in writing to: Oneupweb Attn: Privacy Policy Administrator 1371 Gray Drive, Suite 100 Traverse City, MI 49684
What If I Have Questions?
If you have any questions, concerns or feel that Oneupweb is not following its stated Privacy Policy, you may contact us at info@oneupweb.com. Please include “Privacy Policy Inquiries” in the subject line of your email message.
